affiliateseeking.com 2017-12-21

# AffiliateSeeking.com :: Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy Last Updated:** 13 December 2012

**Why we collect and use your personal information**  
AffiliateSeeking.com collects some personal information from you. This is so we can reply to any site submissions you make within different parts of our site, to contact you if we need to once you joined our forum, etc. The information we collect from you also enables us to contact you from time to time about new offers, features and updates that we have on our site. The personal information we collect from you may include, but is not limited to your name, email address and your websites details/information. 

Some of the other information we may collect from you, is information so that we can monitor our success and performance as a business online. This information could include things like the browser you are using, the time of your visit, how long you was on our site, etc.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

**How we gather users information**  
The way we gather information depends on the section of our site. We may ask you for contact information, which will only be used to contact you about your sites submission or about site updates and offers that we may have plus a few other possible reasons. We will never gather your personal information without your knowledge or understanding. 

When you visit our site, we will also collect information about your visit. This may include the time of day you visited our site, how long you were on our site, etc. We do this so we can better understand the way our visitors use our site, we can then therefore better assist our visitors to provide them with the services they are likely to be most interested in.

**Cookies**  
We at AffiliateSeeking do not directly use cookies, but we do use a 3rd party stats provider and also 3rd party advertising providers like Adsense. The Stats provider and 3rd party advertising providers may use cookies while showing ads on our website and collect statistics or other information. They may also use cookies for other purposes.

**Your personal information and other companies'**  
What ever personally information you submit to our site, we will not sell, rent or trade your information to other companies.

**Security of your personal information**  
AffiliateSeeking.com stores personal information behind selected security devices to help protect your information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure.

**Privacy Policy Agreement**  
By using AffiliateSeeking.com you agree on the way we collect and use your personal information as outlined in this Privacy Policy.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
Our privacy policy may occasionally be updated from time to time. When we do update our privacy policy we will also update the "Privacy Policy Last Updated" date at the top of this page. As our privacy policy may be updated from time to time, we encourage you to occasionally visit this page to check if our policy has been updated or not.
